170,000 sq miles of desert. 90 minutes of oxygen. No way out.
Buried is a drama, thriller, mystery film directed by Rodrigo Cortés.
Paul is a U.S.
truck driver working in Iraq.
After an attack by a group of Iraqis he wakes to find
he is buried alive inside a coffin.
With only a lighter and a cell phone it's a race against
time to escape this claustrophobic death trap.
Paul Conroy, played by Ryan Reynolds.
Jabir (voice), played by José Luis García Pérez.
Dan Brenner (voice), played by Robert Paterson.
Alan Davenport (voice), played by Stephen Tobolowsky.
Linda Conroy (voice), played by Samantha Mathis.
Pamela Lutti (voice), played by Ivana Miño.
Buried is a 2010 English-language survival psychological
thriller film directed by Rodrigo Cortés.
It stars Ryan Reynolds and was written by Chris Sparling.
The film follows Iraq-based American civilian truck driver Paul Conroy (Reynolds), who, after being attacked, finds himself buried
alive in a wooden coffin, with only a lighter, flask, flashlight, knife, glowsticks, pen, pencil, and a mobile phone.
Since its premiere at the 2010 Sundance Film Festival, the
film has received a positive critical reception.
The film explores themes of race against time,
isolation, coffin, buried alive, survival.
The tone is mind_bending and emotional and intense.